RONALD ERICKSEN

LAS VEGAS, NV
PHONE 702-767-7281
E-MAIL RERICKSEN@MSN.COM
PORTFOLIO@ WWW.COROFLOT.COM/PUDD112

SUMMARY

ACCOMPLISHED DESIGN LEADER WITH 10+ YEARS OF EXPERIENCE DESIGNING PRODUCTS AND GRAPHICS THAT ACHIEVED NATIONAL AND INTERNATIONAL SUCCESS. TECHNICALLY SOUND PROFESSIONAL WHO HAS LED ART DEPARTMENTS WHILE CONTRIBUTING MY VERSATILE DESIGN SKILLS THAT ALIGN WITH THE CORPORATE VISION. LOOKING TO HIT THE GROUND RUNNING IN A POSITION THAT UTILIZES MY CREATIVITY. OPEN TO RELOCATION IN THE U.S.

TECHNICAL SKILLS & QUALIFICATIONS

- **EXCEPTIONAL SKILLS UTILIZING ADOBE CREATIVE SUITE, PHOTOSHOP, AFTER EFFECTS, AND KEYNOTE**
- ⊕ DELIVERS RESULTS; 10+ YEARS OF CREATIVE ACCOMPLISHMENTS
- INVENTIVE ARTISTIC ABILITIES, STRONG DATA BASE ORGANIZATION, AND DEPARTMENT MANAGEMENT SKILLS
- OUTSTANDING LAYOUT, LOGO DESIGN, PRODUCTION, WEB GRAPHICS, TYPOGRAPHY, AND ILLUSTRATION SKILLS
- \oplus SKILLED IN MARKETING, WEB, AND PROMOTIONAL STRATEGIES; VENDOR RELATIONS

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

- ⊕ EXCELLED WITHIN CREATIVE DEPARTMENTS FOR A VARIETY OF INDUSTRIES; ADVERTISING, SLOT MACHINE/TABLE GAME DEVELOPMENT, PRODUCT DEVELOPMENT, PRINT MEDIA, CASINO/HOSPITALITY CREATIVE SERVICES, AND TRADE SHOW CREATIVE SERVICES
- SUCCESSFULLY OVERSAW DESIGN AND DEVELOPMENT OF TWO DISTINCT MANUFACTURED PRODUCT LINES
- ⊕ Instrumental in the design of Licensed products that sold thousands of Units Nationally and in International Markets
- ⊕ INITIATED AND DEVELOPED MARKETING AND PACKAGING GRAPHICS ENABLING MY EMPLOYERS TO PROSPER AND REACH RECORD SALES QUOTAS
- MANAGED CREATIVE DEPARTMENTS AND MAINTAINED & IMPLEMENTED SOFTWARE, COMPUTER WORKSTATIONS, AND PERIPHERAL UPGRADES TO STREAMLINE CREATIVE OUTPUT
- DESIGN AND PRODUCTION OF ADVERTISING COLLATERAL THAT HAS GENERATED 5:1 ROI FOR LT GAME/EMPIRE

11/2019-CURRENT: SENIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER, LT GAME/EMPIRE TECHNOLOGICAL GROUP, LAS VEGAS, NV

05/2017 - 10-2019: SENIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER, 112TH STREET DESIGN, LAS VEGAS, NV

04/2017 - 04-2015: SENIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER, GEARBUBBLE, LAS VEGAS, NV

02/2014-05-2014: SENIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER, THE PALAZZO, LAS VEGAS, NV

02/2012-04-2014: GRAPHIC DEPARTMENT MANAGER, GEM MARKETING AND ADVERTISING, LAS VEGAS, NV

09/2010-10-2011: SENIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER, TSF-IMAGEMAX, LAS VEGAS, NV

12/2015-05-2019: ADJUNCT INSTRUCTOR FOR UNLV'S GRAPHIC DESIGN UNDERGRADUATE DEGREE PROGRAM

ADDITIONAL WORK EXPERIENCE:

OFF ICE OFFICIAL NHL, LAS VEGAS GOLDEN KNIGHTS 03/2017-09/2021

ON ICE OFFICIAL LVHOA, LAS VEGAS, NV CURRENT

ARTIST III, IGT, LAS VEGAS NV

SENIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER, IMPERIAL PALACE HOTEL CASINO LAS VEGAS, NV

EDUCATION

AMERICAN ACADEMY OF ART, CHICAGO, IL RAY VOGUE COLLEGE OF DESIGN, CHICAGO, IL